
up to date, audited 615 packages in 2s

65 packages are looking for funding
  run `npm fund` for details

9 vulnerabilities (1 moderate, 8 high)

To address issues that do not require attention, run:
  npm audit fix

To address all issues possible (including breaking changes), run:
  npm audit fix --force

Some issues need review, and may require choosing
a different dependency.

Run `npm audit` for details.
